Guide to the Walt Horan Papers 1939-1967
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 6: Legislation, 1943-1964
  - Horan
    - 1949: H.R. 1325, To provide additional income tax exemptions to widowed heads of families (Box 381, Folder 7453)
    - 1949: H.R. 1326, To encourage development of new domestic sources of zinc ores by amending the Tariff Act of 1930 as amended (Box 381, Folder 7454)
    - 1949: H.R. 1327 to amend the Internal Revenue Code so as to exempt air taxis from provisions of the transportation tax (Box 381, Folder 7455)
    - 1949: H.R. 2484, authorize grants to Ferry and Okanogan Counties in lieu of taxes (Box 381, Folder 7456)
    - 1949: to establish a Columbia Interstate Commission and for other purposes (Box 381, Folder 7457)
    - 1949: H.R. 2432, restoring to Tribal ownership certain lands on Colville Reservation (Box 381, Folder 7458)
    - 1949: Indian Bill, H.R. 2387 (formally H.R. 2432) (Box 381, Folder 7459-7463)
    - 1949: Indian Bill, H.R. 2387 (formerly H.R. 2432) (continued) (Box 382, Folder 7464)
    - 1950: Remarks, "American Foreign Policy" (Box 382, Folder 7465)
    - 1950: Political Issues Survey, Washington State (Box 382, Folder 7466)
    - 1950: U.S. Must sell Freedom Idea to Survive (Box 382, Folder 7467)
    - 1950: Remarks, You can't do business with the Soviets (Box 382, Folder 7468)
    - 1950: Remarks, The permanent Point 4 (Box 382, Folder 7469)
    - 1950: Remarks, Point 4 Au Jus (Box 382, Folder 7470)
    - 1950: Labor Day Message (Box 382, Folder 7471)
    - 1950: Albeni Falls Record on passage of supplemental funds (Box 382, Folder 7472)
    - 1950: Power-Henry J. Kaiser release (Box 382, Folder 7473)
    - 1950: "East says they have enough power" from Daily World (Box 382, Folder 7474)
    - 1950: Communism vs. Christianity (Box 382, Folder 7475)
    - 1950: Mining Equipment for Yugoslavia, Frank Lilly's Letter (Box 382, Folder 7476)
    - 1950: Production of Aluminum and other light metals (Box 382, Folder 7477)
    - 1950: Grass roots farm bill (H.R. 9093) speech reprinted (Box 382, Folder 7478)
    - 1950: The real tragedy of Forrestal (Box 382, Folder 7479)
    - 1950: Statement of Spokane Chamber of Commerce (Box 382, Folder 7480)
    - 1950: Rent decontrol has helped Spokane (Extension remarks) (Box 382, Folder 7481)
    - 1950: Today's Dollar Tomorrow, Lilly (Box 382, Folder 7482)
    - 1950: Leon Starment's articles on Columbia Basin (Box 382, Folder 7483)
    - 1950: Explanatory statement, H.R. 7478 (Box 382, Folder 7484)
    - 1950: Report on Grazing Lands (1947-1949) (Box 382, Folder 7485)
    - 1950: Brannan Plan (Box 382, Folder 7486)
    - 1950: "The Old Order changeth, Yielding Place to the new" (speech for Bible class, not given) (Box 382, Folder 7487)
    - 1950: A Fable about Potato prices (Dave Kirk) (Box 382, Folder 7488)
    - 1950: National Capitol Sesquicentennial (Horan's speech on Capitol steps, April 15) (Box 382, Folder 7489)
    - 1950: William Lemke's passing (Box 382, Folder 7490)
    - 1950: The late Rufus Woods (Box 382, Folder 7491)
    - 1950: Grass Roots Comment, Frank Shields letter and Roger Hale letter (Box 382, Folder 7492)
    - 1950: Speech before Art Minor's Bible class, on civilization and love (Box 382, Folder 7493)
    - 1950: Commodity Credit debate on Floor (H.R. 6567) (Box 382, Folder 7494)
    - 1950: Sesquicentennial Speech, Frances Yeend Concert (Box 383, Folder 7495)
    - 1950: Explanation of H.R. 7149, S. 2996 (Box 383, Folder 7496)
    - 1950: Senator Schoeppel of Kansas speech. Lincoln Day, Wenatchee (Box 383, Folder 7497)
    - 1950: Coal Strike Speech (Box 383, Folder 7498)
    - 1950: U.S. Tariff and Europe's Quotas (Box 383, Folder 7499)
    - 1949-1950: Addition Income Tax Exemption, widowed Heads of families, H.R. 1325 (Box 383, Folder 7500)
    - 1950: Testimony, imports (Box 383, Folder 7501)
    - 1950: H.R. 4430 to exempt Engelmann spruce lumber from import tax of Internal Revenue Code (Box 383, Folder 7502)
    - 1950: H.J. Res. 520, Amending Armed Services Procurement Act of 1947 to provide protection for those not covered by workmen's compensation laws (Box 383, Folder 7503)
    - 1950: H.R. 8613--Pub law 665 Loans through RACC (Box 383, Folder 7504)
    - 1950: H.R. 9094 Provide benefits for persons serving on revenue cutter Bear during Arctic rescue cruise (Box 383, Folder 7505)
    - 1950: H.R. 9093, Grange Farm Bill (Box 383, Folder 7506)
    - 1950: H.R. 7478 Creating Commission on Fed reimbursement to States and local govts (Box 383, Folder 7507)
    - 1950: H.Res. 603, For. Affairs Cmt (Bill introduced by others, including Javitz) (Box 383, Folder 7508)
    - 1950: H. R. 4430, Exempt Engelmann Spruce lumber from import tax (Box 383, Folder 7509)
    - 1950: H.R. 7478, Creating a Commission on Federal reimbursement to states and local govts. etc. (Box 383, Folder 7510)
    - 1950: H. J. Res. 520, Armed Services (Box 383, Folder 7511)
    - 1950: H.R. 8613, Loans in Lieu of RAAC (Box 383, Folder 7512-7513)
    - 1950: H. R. 4113 Amend Section 6 of River and Harbor Act of 1946 (Box 383, Folder 7514)
    - 1950: Complete file of Walt Horan's bills, 81st Congress (Box 383, Folder 7515)
    - 1951: H.R. 2268 Testimony (Box 384, Folder 7516)
    - 1952: H.R. 2470, D'Ewart's Bill (Box 384, Folder 7517)
    - 1951: Statement, H.R. 4963, Jackson's elec. generating plant (Box 384, Folder 7518)
    - 1951: Statement on H.R. 910, Nurses Bill (Box 384, Folder 7519)
    - 1951: Best Remedy for inflation, letter of Fred Phelps (Box 384, Folder 7520)
    - 1951: It's Your Food Supply (Box 384, Folder 7521)
    - 1951: Truman-MacArthur situation (Box 384, Folder 7522)
    - 1951: Farm Labor Subcommittee statement (Box 384, Folder 7523)
    - 1951: Richland's New School (Box 384, Folder 7524)
    - 1951: An Outstanding Job progress edition of Review (Box 384, Folder 7525)
    - 1951: Freight Rates Increase Protest (Box 384, Folder 7526)
    - 1951: "Valuation of Gold by Great Britain, Frank Lilly Letters (Box 384, Folder 7527)
    - 1953-1955: Scale of Town of Coulee Dam, Wash.--Correspondence (Box 384, Folder 7528-7531)
    - 1953-1955: Scale of Town of Coulee Dam, Wash--Correspondence (continued) (Box 385, Folder 7532-7534)
    - 1953-1955: H.R. 2932, For the Relief of John H. Miller (Box 385, Folder 7535)
    - 1951-1955: H.R. 2931, Relief of Gina Bellagamba (Box 385, Folder 7356)
    - 1955: Roland Mead Daly, Funeral (Box 385, Folder 7357)
    - 1955: Steve Nyman (Sandy's Friend) (Box 385, Folder 7538)
    - 1955: Committee Appearances (Box 385, Folder 7539)
    - 1955-1956: H.R. 5678, For the Relief of Dr. Roughi (Box 385, Folder 7540)
    - 1948-1955: H.R. 2933, Relief of Berta Mansergh (Box 385, Folder 7541)
    - 1956-1957: Nye Yen Woo (Box 386, Folder 7542)
    - 1954-1955: H.R. 2139 Lake Behind McNary Dam to be called Lake Wallula (Box 386, Folder 7543)
    - 1949-1956: H.R. 2288, Sylvia Simonson (Box 386, Folder 7544-7545)
    - 1958-1959: Nick Simchuk (Box 386, Folder 7546)
    - 1957: H.R. 3388 provide for licensing of TV reflector facilities and VHF translator facilities (Box 386, Folder 7547)
    - 1957: H.R. 685, Amend Federal Aid Highway Act of 1944 to provide for an addition to the National system of Interstate Highways (Box 386, Folder 7548)
    - 1956-1959: 4044, For the Relief of Mirko J. Pitner (Box 386, Folder 7549)
    - 1956: Omak Lake (Box 386, Folder 7550)
    - 1956: Lionel Tsao (Box 386, Folder 7551)
    - 1954-1956: H.R. 1918, Hal Marchant, Trade rights for Vessel Jenny (Box 386, Folder 7552)
    - 1956: H.R. 10605, Soil Bank Bill (Box 386, Folder 7553)
    - 1956: H.R. 8734, Bankhead-Jones amendments, Agriculture (Box 386, Folder 7554-7555)
    - 1955-1957: H.R. 2934, Relief of Maria Pizzarella (Box 386, Folder 7556)
    - 1955-1957: H.R. 2934, Relief of Maria Pizzarella (continued) (Box 387, Folder 7557)
    - 1957: H.R. 3389, Disposal of Federal property in Coulee Dam and Grand Coulee areas (Box 387, Folder 7558)
    - 1958-1959: Fort George Wright Cemetery, Spokane (Box 387, Folder 7559-7563)
    - 1958-1959: Fort George Wright Cemetery, Spokane (continued) (Box 388, Folder 7564)
    - 1960-1961: Fort George Wright Cemetery, Spokane (Box 388, Folder 7565-7568)
    - 1959-1960: H.R. 1125, Union Recognition (H.R. 11191, 81st) (Box 388, Folder 7569)
    - 1958-1959: H.R. 11294, George Shiosaki (Box 388, Folder 7570)
    - 1954-1960: H.R. 3410, Relief of Mrs. Leonard Erickson (H.R. 4045, 85th) (Box 388, Folder 7571)
    - 1958-1959: H.R. 802, Town of Bridgeport Wash. (H.R. 13215, 85th) (Box 389, Folder 7572)
    - 1945-1959: H.R. 3808, Award of Medal to Hugh Herndon, Jr. and posthumously to Clyde Pangborn (H.R. 4043, 85th) (Box 389, Folder 7573)
    - 1959: Century 21 Exposition, H.R. 7431 (Box 389, Folder 7574)
    - 1957-1959: Columbia Interstate Commission Bill (Box 389, Folder 7575)
    - 1957-1958: H.R. 9058, amend Internal Revenue Code (Box 389, Folder 7576)
    - 1958: H. Con. Res 275, National Aviation Week (Box 389, Folder 7577)
    - 1958: H.J. Res 492, Establishing a commission on REA Loan Programs (Box 389, Folder 7578)
    - 1961: H.R. 7650, Banks Lake Reservoir (Box 389, Folder 7579)
    - 1961: H.R. 4829, Oroville Tonasket Chief Joseph Dam Project (Box 389, Folder 7580-7582)
    - 1954-1962: H.R. 7136 Oroville-Tonasket unit of Okanogan-Similkameen Div. Chief Joseph Dam (Box 390, Folder 7583-7584)
    - 1954-1962: Oroville-Tonasket Project, Public Law 762, 87th Congress (Box 390, Folder 7585-7587)
    - 1961-1962: Authorize use of funds arising from judgments in favor of any of Confederated Tribes of Colville Reservation, Public Law 298, 87th Congress (Box 390, Folder 7588-7589)
    - 1958-1960: To Equalize pay of retired members of uniformed service (Box 390, Folder 7590)
    - 1962: H.R. 9879, amend Merchant Marine Act of 1920 (Box 391, Folder 7591)
    - 1961-1962: H.R. 9133, Marketing programs for Wheat (Box 391, Folder 7592)
    - 1961: H.R. 6620, Union Recognition, 87th Congress (Box 391, Folder 7593)
    - 1961: H.R. 5784, Tax Relief for small business, 87th Congress (Box 391, Folder 7594)
    - 1961: FHA Loan Modernization bill, enacted into Public Law in 87th Congress (Box 391, Folder 7595)
    - 1963-1964: H.R. 8765, For Relief of Kenneth York Sue (Box 391, Folder 7596)
    - 1964: Wesel Oviatt Lumber Co. (Box 391, Folder 7597)
    - 1963-1964: H.J. Res 477, Relating to Father's Day (Box 391, Folder 7598)
    - 1949-1962: H.J. Res. 451, Father's Day (Box 391, Folder 7599-7600)
    - 1961-1963: H.R. 3749, For the relief of Mr. and Mrs. Wm Roberts (Box 391, Folder 7601)
    - 1963: Propane Gas (Box 392, Folder 7602)
    - 1963-1964: H.J. Res 988, Gold Medal for Henry J. Kaiser (Box 392, Folder 7603)
    - 1961: Lionel Theen (Paauw's friend) (Box 392, Folder 7604)
    - 1961-1963: H.R. 11123, Immigration, Hyung Jin Kim (Box 392, Folder 7605)
    - 1961: H.R. 6904, Transportation Bill, Water Carrier Exemptions (Box 392, Folder 7606)
    - 1961-1962: H.R. 9181, Relief of Hong-Kyw Cho (Box 392, Folder 7607)
    - 1961-1964: Legislation: Horan: H.R. 8469 Colville Termination (Box 392, Folder 7608-7609)
    - 1960: H.R. 7201 (Box 392, Folder 7610)
    - 1960: H.R. 7201 Headwater Benefits Bill (Box 392, Folder 7611)
    - 1960-1961: H.R. 5006, River Management, Headwater Benefits (Box 392, Folder 7612)
    - 1953-1963: H.R. 1124, Relocation of Ferry County Highway (H.R. 4784, 85th) (Box 393, Folder 7613)
    - 1954: Landslide Conditions along Ferry County Highway paralleling Lake Roosevelt From Kettle Falls to Mouth of Spokane River, Wash. by Fred O. Jones (Box 393, Folder 7614)
    - 1958-1963: H.R. 5922, Relocation of Ferry County Highway (Box 393, Folder 7615)
    - 1960: H.R. 10555 (Box 393, Folder 7616)
    - 1963-1964: H. R. 5118, Whitestone Coulee Unit (Box 393, Folder 7617-7619)
    - 1964: H.R. 10257, Banks Lakes and Potholes (Box 393, Folder 7620)
    - 1963-1964: Spokane Valley (Box 393, Folder 7621)
    - 1963: Chief Joseph Reclamation Bill (Box 393, Folder 7622)
    - 1962-1963: Chelan-Manson Irrigation Project (Box 394, Folder 7623)
    - 1964: Chelan-Manson Project (Box 394, Folder 7624)
    - 1960-1962: Agriculture and Forestry (Box 394, Folder 7625)
    - 1964: Kalispell Judgment Fund Bill, H.R. 10973 (Box 394, Folder 7626)
    - 1963: H.R. 4535 Funds arising from Colville Judgment funds (Box 394, Folder 7627-7628)
    - 1963: H.R. 7166, Colville Termination (Box 394, Folder 7629)
    - 1963: H.R. 6555, Feed Grain and Wheat Proposal (Box 394, Folder 7630-7631)
    - 1963: H.R. 7187, Mexican Agricultural Workers (Box 394, Folder 7632)
    - 1964: H.R. 9412 Amend Tariff Act, re Cattle, beef, and veal imports (Box 394, Folder 7633-7634)
    - 1963-1964: Termination Legislation (Colville Tribes) (Box 395, Folder 7635-7636)
    - 1963: H.J. Res. 256, Quota on softwood lumber imports (Box 395, Folder 7637-7638)
    - 1962: H.J. Res. 735, Relief for Lumber Industry (Box 395, Folder 7639)
    - 1963-1964: Miscellaneous Press release statements (Box 395, Folder 7640)
    - 1963-1964: H.R. 3951, To declare wood an agricultural commodity (Box 395, Folder 7641)
    - 1963: H.R. 3955, To amend the National Housing Act relative to use of American timber (Box 396, Folder 7642)
    - 1963: H.R. 3691 (Box 396, Folder 7643)
    - 1963: H. Res. 122, Prohibit back door spending (Box 396, Folder 7644)
    - 1963: H. Res 408, Select committee on fiscal organization (Box 396, Folder 7645)
    - 1963: H. Res. 299, "Price tag on House bills" (Box 396, Folder 7646)
    - 1963-1964: H. R. 6270, Lead-Zinc (Box 396, Folder 7647)
    - 1962: H.R. 9974, Lead-Zinc Bill (Box 396, Folder 7648)
    - 1963-1964: H.R. 3690, Quality Stabilization (Box 396, Folder 7649-7650)
    - 1963: H.R. 3956, Work measurement in the Post Office (Box 396, Folder 7651)
    - 1963: H.J. Res. 346, Equal Rights (Box 396, Folder 7652)
    - 1962: H.J. Res 692, Equal Rights (Box 396, Folder 7653)
  - Legislation: Miscellaneous
    - 1948 (Box 396, Folder 7654)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 396, Folder 7655)
    - 1947 (Box 397, Folder 7655-7656)
    - 1950 (Box 397, Folder 7657-7659)
    - 1949 (Box 397, Folder 7660-7661)
    - 1949 (continued) (Box 398, Folder 7662)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 398, Folder 7663)
    - 1953 (Box 398, Folder 7664-7665)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 398, Folder 7666)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 398, Folder 7667)
    - 1951 (Box 398, Folder 7668)
    - 1954 (Box 399, Folder 7669-7672)
    - 1956 (Box 399, Folder 7673-7674)
    - 1956 (Box 400, Folder 7675-7676)
    - 1955 (Box 400, Folder 7677-7678)
    - 1957 (Box 400, Folder 7679-7680)
    - 1957(continued) (Box 401, Folder 7681-7683)
    - 1958 (Box 401, Folder 7684-7686)
    - 1958 (continued) (Box 402, Folder 7687-7689)
    - 1959 (Box 402, Folder 7690-7692)
    - 1959 (continued) (Box 403, Folder 76937695)
    - 1960 (Box 403, Folder 7696-7697)
    - 1960 (continued) (Box 404, Folder 7698-7699)
    - 1961 (Box 404, Folder 7700-7703)
    - 1961 (continued) (Box 405, Folder 7704-7707)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 405, Folder 7708)
    - 1962 (Box 405, Folder 7709)
    - 1962 (continued) (Box 406, Folder 7710-7715)
    - 1962 (continued) (Box 407, Folder 7716-7717)
    - 1963 (Box 407, Folder 7718-7720)
    - 1963 (Box 408, Folder 7721-7725)
    - 1964 (Box 408, Folder 7726)
    - 1964 (continued) (Box 409, Folder 7727-7729)
- Series 7: Communication with Constituents, 1945-1964
  - Newsletters
    - 1964 (Box 410, Folder 7730)
    - 1964 (Box 410, Folder 7731)
    - 1962 (Box 410, Folder 7732)
    - 1961 (Box 410, Folder 7733)
    - 1960 (Box 410, Folder 7734)
    - 1959 (Box 410, Folder 7735)
    - 1958 (Box 410, Folder 7736)
    - 1957 (Box 410, Folder 7737)
    - 1956 (Box 410, Folder 7738)
    - 1955 (Box 410, Folder 7739)
    - 1954 (Box 410, Folder 7740)
    - 1953 (Box 410, Folder 7741)
    - 1952 (Box 410, Folder 7742)
    - 1951 (Box 410, Folder 7743)
    - 1950 (Box 410, Folder 7744)
    - 1949 (Box 410, Folder 7745)
    - 1948 (Box 410, Folder 7746)
    - 1947 (Box 410, Folder 7747)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 410, Folder 7748)
    - 1963-1964: Correspondence (Box 411, Folder 7749)
    - 1960-1962: Correspondence (Box 411, Folder 7750)
    - 1956-1960: Correspondence (Box 411, Folder 7751)
    - 1953-1955: Correspondence (Box 411, Folder 7752)
    - 1950-1952: Correspondence (Box 411, Folder 7753)
    - 1949-1950: Correspondence (Box 411, Folder 7754)
    - 1948: Correspondence (Box 411, Folder 7755)
    - 1947: Correspondence (Box 412, Folder 7756)
    - 1945-1946: Correspondence (Box 412, Folder 7757)
  - Radio Broadcasts
    - 1949 (Box 412, Folder 7758-7759)
    - 1950 (Box 412, Folder 7760-7761)
    - 1951 August 1 to October 24 (Box 412, Folder 7762)
    - 1951 March 8 to July 25 (Box 412, Folder 7763)
    - 1951 March 8 to May 9 (Box 413, Folder 7764)
    - 1952 (Box 413, Folder 7765-7766)
    - 1953 (Box 413, Folder 7767-7768)
    - 1953 to February 28, 1954 (Box 413, Folder 7769)
    - 1954 (Box 413, Folder 7770)
    - 1954: Television (Box 414, Folder 7771)
    - 1955-1957 Recordings (Box 414, Folder 7772)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 414, Folder 7773-7774)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 414, Folder 7775-7776)
    - 1957: Correspondence (Box 414, Folder 7777)
    - 1958: Correspondence (Box 414, Folder 7778)
    - 1959: Correspondence (Box 414, Folder 7779)
    - 1951-1954: Correspondence (Box 414, Folder 7780)
    - 1955-1956: Correspondence (Box 415, Folder 7781)
    - 1949-1952: Correspondence (Box 415, Folder 7782-7783)
- Series 8: Political, 1942-1964
  - General and practical politics
    - 1942: Primary (Box 415, Folder 7784)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 415, Folder 7785-7786)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 415, Folder 7787)
    - 1944 (Box 415, Folder 7788)
    - 1944 (Box 416, Folder 7789-7791)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 416, Folder 7792)
    - 1947 (Box 416, Folder 7793-7795)
    - 1947-1950 (Box 417, Folder 7796)
    - 1947-1949 (Box 417, Folder 7797)
    - 1948 (Box 417, Folder 7798)
    - 1948-1951 (Box 417, Folder 7799)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 417, Folder 7800)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 417, Folder 7801-7802)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 418, Folder 7803)
    - 1949-1951 (Box 418, Folder 7804)
    - 1948-1950 (Box 418, Folder 7805)
    - 1950-1952 (Box 418, Folder 7806)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 418, Folder 7807)
    - 1951 (Box 418, Folder 7808)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 418, Folder 7809)
    - 1952: 5th District (Box 419, Folder 7810)
    - 1948-1954 (Box 419, Folder 7811)
    - 1948-1955 (Box 419, Folder 7812)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 419, Folder 7813)
    - 1953-1954: 5th District (Box 419, Folder 7814)
    - 1953-1955 (Box 419, Folder 7815)
    - 1953-1958 (Box 420, Folder 7816)
    - 1955-1957 (Box 420, Folder 7817-7818)
    - 1953-1958 (Box 420, Folder 7819)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 420, Folder 7820)
    - 1956-1958: 5th District (Box 420, Folder 7821)
    - 1955-1956: 5th District (Box 420, Folder 7822)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 421, Folder 7823)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 421, Folder 7824)
    - 1959-1961 (Box 421, Folder 7825)
    - 1959-1962 (Box 421, Folder 7826)
    - 1960 (Box 421, Folder 7827)
    - 1959-1959 (Box 421, Folder 7828)
    - 1958-1962 (Box 421, Folder 7829)
    - 1962 (Box 422, Folder 7830)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 422, Folder 7831-2)
    - 1962 (Box 422, Folder 7833)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 422, Folder 7834)
    - 1963 (Box 422, Folder 7835)
    - 1962-1964 (Box 423, Folder 7836)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 423, Folder 7837)
    - 1963-1964: 5th District (Box 423, Folder 7838-7839)
    - 1949-1963: Lincoln Day (Box 423, Folder 7840)
    - 1953-1960: Lincoln Day (Box 423, Folder 7841)
    - 1951-1957: Lincoln Day (Box 424, Folder 7842)
    - 1950-1952: Lincoln Day (Box 424, Folder 7843)
  - Campaigns
    - 1948 (Box 424, Folder 7844-7848)
    - 1948-1954: 5th District (Box 425, Folder 7849)
    - 1949: 1948 Election, statistical analysis (Box 425, Folder 7850)
    - 1948: Financial (Box 425, Folder 7851)
    - 1948 (Box 425, Folder 7852-7855)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 426, Folder 7856)
    - 1950-1952 (Box 426, Folder 7857)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 426, Folder 7858-7861)
    - 1949 (Box 426, Folder 7862)
    - 1950 (Box 427, Folder 7863-7864)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 427, Folder 7865)
    - 1950 (Box 427, Folder 7866)
    - 1948-1950 (Box 427, Folder 7867)
    - 1949: Compton I. White vs. City of Spokane (Box 427, Folder 7868)
    - 1950 (Box 427, Folder 7869)
    - 1950 (Box 428, Folder 7870-7875)
    - 1950 (Box 429, Folder 7876-7880)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 429, Folder 7881)
    - 1950-1960: Financial (Box 430, Folder 7882-7883)
    - 1950 (Box 430, Folder 7884-7886)
    - 1952-1955: Financial (Box 430, Folder 7887)
    - 1951-1952: "Quick Answers" (Box 430, Folder 7888)
    - 1952 (Box 431, Folder 7889-7890)
    - 1950-1952 (Box 431, Folder 7891)
    - 1952 (Box 431, Folder 7892-7894)
    - 1952 (Box 432, Folder 7895-7899)
    - 1952: Clippings of Primary Figures (Box 432, Folder 7900)
    - 1952: Opposition Campaigns (Box 432, Folder 7901)
    - 1954 (Box 433, Folder 7902-7904)
    - 1953-1954: Quick Answers (Box 433, Folder 7905)
    - 1954: Financial (Box 433, Folder 7906-7907)
    - 1954: Financial (Box 434, Folder 7908)
    - 1954 (Box 434, Folder 7909-9713)
    - 1952-1954 (Box 435, Folder 7914-7916)
    - 1952 (Box 435, Folder 7917)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 435, Folder 7918)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 435, Folder 7919)
    - 1952-1954 (Box 435, Folder 7920)
    - 1952-1954 (continued) (Box 436, Folder 7921)
    - 1956: Our opposition (Box 436, Folder 7922)
    - 1956 (Box 436, Folder 7923)
    - 1956: Financial (Box 436, Folder 7924-7928)
    - 1956 (Box 437, Folder 7929-7934)
    - 1956 (continued) (Box 438, Folder 7935-7937)
    - 1958 (Box 438, Folder 7938-7940)
    - 1958 (continued) (Box 439, Folder 7941-7942)
    - 1958: Opposition (Box 439, Folder 7943-7944)
    - 1958: Campaign: Financials (Box 439, Folder 7945)
    - 1958 (Box 439, Folder 7946-7947)
    - 1958 (continued) (Box 440, Folder 7948)
    - 1960 (Box 440, Folder 7949)
    - 1958 (Box 440, Folder 7950)
    - 1948-1956 (Box 440, Folder 7951)
    - 1960 (Box 440, Folder 7952)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 440, Folder 7953)
    - 1960 (Box 441, Folder 7954-7956)
    - 1960: Financial (Box 441, Folder 7957)
    - 1960: Summary and Career to 1958 (Box 441, Folder 7958)
    - 1960 (Box 441, Folder 7959)
    - 1960 (continued) (Box 442, Folder 7960-7962)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 442, Folder 7963)
    - 1962 (Box 442, Folder 7964-7965)
    - 1962 (continued) (Box 443, Folder 7966-7969)
    - 1962: Financial (Box 443, Folder 7970)
    - 1964 (Box 443, Folder 7971)
    - 1964 (continued) (Box 444, Folder 7972-7973)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 444, Folder 7974)
    - 1962-1964 (continued) (Box 444, Folder 7975)
    - 1964 (Box 444, Folder 7976)
    - 1964: Opposition (Box 444, Folder 7977)
    - 1964 (Box 445, Folder 7978-7980)
    - 1959-1964 (Box 445, Folder 7981)
    - 1964 (Box 445, Folder 7982)
    - 1964: John Birch Society (Box 445, Folder 7983-7984)
  - Speech Kits
    - 1958 (Box 446, Folder 7985)
    - 1956 (Box 446, Folder 7986)
    - 1954 (Box 446, Folder 7987)
    - 1952 (Box 446, Folder 7988)
    - 1949 (Box 446, Folder 7989)
    - 1963 (Box 447, Folder 7990)
    - 1964: Supplements (Box 447, Folder 7991)
    - 1959 (Box 447, Folder 7992)
    - 1960 (Box 447, Folder 7993)
  - Politics in Congress
    - 1948-1955 (Box 447, Folder 7994)
    - 1945-1955 (Box 447, Folder 7995)
    - 1944-1964 (Box 448, Folder 7996)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 448, Folder 7997)
    - 1950-1963 (Box 448, Folder 7998)
    - 1947-1949 (Box 448, Folder 7999-8000)
    - 1947-1950 (Box 448, Folder 8001)
    - 1944-1955 (Box 449, Folder 8002)
    - 1945-1947 (Box 449, Folder 8003)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 449, Folder 8004)
    - 1961: President's Message (Box 449, Folder 8005)
  - Inaugurals
    - 1952-1957 (Box 449, Folder 8006)
    - 1948-1957 (Box 449, Folder 8007)
  - Patronage
    - 1958-1959: Federal Judge Sam Drive Replacement (Box 450, Folder 8008)